let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: " This set of Artificial Intelligence Multiple Choice Questions & Answers (MCQs) focuses on Machine Learning?",
        answer: "The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs",
        options: [
            "The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs",
            "The autonomous acquisition of knowledge through the use of manual programs",
            "The selective acquisition of knowledge through the use of computer programs",
            "The selective acquisition of knowledge through the use of manual programs"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: " Which of the factors affect the performance of learner system does not include?",
        answer: " Good data structures",
        options: [
            "Representation scheme used",
            "Training scenario",
            "Type of feedback",
            "Good data structures"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Different learning methods does not include?",
        answer: " Introduction",
        options: [
            "Memorization",
            "Analogy",
            "Deduction",
            "Introduction"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: " In language understanding, the levels of knowledge that does not include?",
        answer: " Empirical",
        options: [
            "Phonological",
            "Syntactic",
            "Empirical",
            "Logical",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "A model of language consists of the categories which does not include?",
        answer: " Structural units",
        options: [
            "Language units",
            "Role structure of units",
            "System constraints",
            "Structural units"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: " What is a top-down parser?",
        answer: " Begins by hypothesizing a sentence (the symbol S) and successively predicting lower level constituents until individual preterminal symbols are written",
        options: [
            "Begins by hypothesizing a sentence (the symbol S) and successively predicting lower level constituents until individual preterminal symbols are written",
            "Begins by hypothesizing a sentence (the symbol S) and successively predicting upper level constituents until individual preterminal symbols are written",
            "Begins by hypothesizing lower level constituents and successively predicting a sentence (the symbol S)",
            "Begins by hypothesizing upper level constituents and successively predicting a sentence (the symbol S)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: " Among the following which is not a horn clause?",
        answer: " p → Øq",
        options: [
            "p",
            "Øp V q",
            "p → q",
            "p → Øq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: " The action STACK(A, B) of a robot arm specify to ______________?",
        answer: " Place block A on block B",
        options: [
            "Place block B on Block A",
            "Place blocks A, B on the table in that order",
            " Place blocks B, A on the table in that order",
            "Place block A on block B"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The action STACK(A, B) of a robot arm specify to ______________?",
        answer: " Place block A on block B",
        options: [
            "Place block B on Block A",
            "Place blocks A, B on the table in that order",
            "Place blocks B, A on the table in that order",
            "Place block A on block B"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " What is true about Machine Learning?",
        answer: " All of the above",
        options: [
            "Machine Learning (ML) is that field of computer science",
            "ML is a type of artificial intelligence that extract patterns out of raw data by using an algorithm or method",
            "The main focus of ML is to allow computer systems learn from experience without being explicitly programmed or human intervention",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: " ML is a field of AI consisting of learning algorithms that?",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
            "Improve their performance",
            "At executing some task",
            "Over time with experience",
            "All of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " p → 0q is not a?",
        answer: " horn clause",
        options: [
            "hack clause",
            "horn clause",
            "structural clause",
            "system clause"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: " The action _______ of a robot arm specify to Place block A on block B?",
        answer: " STACK(A,B)",
        options: [
            "STACK(A,B)",
            "horn clausLIST(A,B)",
            "QUEUE(A,B)",
            "ARRAY(A,B)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: " A__________ begins by hypothesizing a sentence and successively predicting lower level constituents until individual preterminal symbols are written?",
        answer: " top-down parser",
        options: [
            "bottow-up parser",
            "top parser",
            "top-down parser",
            "bottom parser"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "A model of language consists of the categories which does not include ________. ?",
        answer: "structural units",
        options: [
            "data units",
            "empirical units",
            "structural units",
            "System Unit"
        ]
    },
];